Guide to the Thomas B. Deen papers, 1957-1995
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Meetings and Events, April 1962-October 1994
  - 50th Annual Meeting-Institute of Transportation Engineers, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, July-August 1980 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 40th Annual Maine Transportation Conference, September-December 1989 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Transportation and Economic Development, August-November 1989 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - TV Taping, August-October 1989 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Strategic Highway Research Program, Gothenburg, Sweden, August-October 1989 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Brookings Institution, March-October 1989 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Transportation Research Board and Department of Transportation Relations, June-September 1989 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Transportation Research Board and Department of Transportation-National Academy of Science, June-August 1989 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - World Conference on Transport Research-Society (WCTRS), Japan 1989, December 1986-April 1988 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Seattle, April-July 1989 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Western Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials Research Advisory Committee Meeting, Phoenix, Arizona, March-June 1989 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Meeting with Secretary of Transportation Samuel K. Skinner, February-June 1989 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - China/Korea 1 of 2, January 1987-March 1989 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - China/Korea 2 of 2, July 1986-March 1992 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - International Road Federation Seoul, Korea, 1985-May 1989 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Institute of Transportation Engineers International Conference, Dallas, Texas, January-May 1989 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Houston, Texas, February-March 1989 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Center for Transportation Studies, August 1988-January 1989 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Kentucky Annual Transportation Forum, November 1988-May 1989 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Auburn, Alabama, June 1988-January 1989 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Transportation Alternatives Group, October-November 1988 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Colorado Transportation Conference, July-November 1988 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Frank Mulvey, October 1988 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Permanent International Association of Road Congress- Morocco, January-October 1991 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Permanent International Association of Road Congress- Spain, October 1990-September 1991 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - National Center for Asphalt Technology- Chicago, April-August 1991 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Meeting with Warren Hoemann, July 1991 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - International Symposium on Highway Capacity, December 1990-August 1991 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Urban Mass Transportation Administration-Orlando, January 1990-May 1991 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Department of Transportation-National Academy of Science Forum, February-May 1991 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - National Civil Engineering Research Needs Forum, November 1990-January 1991 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Corps of Engineers Meeting, October 1990-January 1991 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Environmental and Energy Study Institute-Surface Transportation Meeting Registration, June-October 1990 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - National Governors Meeting, August-September 1990 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Western Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials Meeting, January-August 1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Highway- Intelligent Vehicle, May 1990 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - High Occupancy Vehicle Meeting Washington, April 1990 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Airlie House Meeting, December 1989-January 1990 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - French Road Delegation Visitors, November-December 1992 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - American Public Transit Association Luncheon, March-October 1992 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - The National Transit Institute- Torrey, July-October 1992 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Civil Engineering Research Foundation Workshops, June-November 1992 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Transport, Highways and Planning Meeting, July-September 1992 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Civil Engineering Research Foundation Workshops, March 1990-October 1992 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Transportation Forum, March-July 1992 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Joint Center for Urban Mobility Research-Rice Center, Houston, Texas, February-September 1987 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Joint Center for Urban Mobility Research-Rice Center, Houston, Texas, November 1985-June 1986 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Joint Center for Urban Mobility Research-Rice Center, Houston, Texas, March-June 1985 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - International Road Federation, April 1991-November 1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - University of California, January-May 1992 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Truck Conference, March 1990-April 1992 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Advantage I-75 Conference, University of Kentucky, February-April 1992 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - National Center for Asphalt Technology, August 1991-March 1992 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - First Annual Report to the President and Congress, March-June 1992 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Auto Safety Foundation with Highway Users Federation for Safety and Mobility, January-March 1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society of America Coordinating Council Meeting, November 1991-February 1992 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - National Center for Asphalt Technology Meeting- The 26th Annual Report, August-December 1991 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Planning and Research Workshop, January-December 1991 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - The Ditchley Foundation, April-October 1991 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Permanent International Association of Road Congress 1991- September and December Meetings, September 1991-January 1992 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Permanent International Association of Road Congress- Backgrounds, August-November 1990 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society of America, Newport, California, March-May 1992 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - International Bridge, Tunnel and Turnpike Association, January-May 1992 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Permanent International Association of Road Congress, June 1990-September 1991 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Morgan State University, October 1991-June 1992 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials Policy Committee Meeting Grand Lakes, Oklahoma, June-September 1981 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials Annual Meeting Chicago, IL, October 1978-October 1981 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials Article, January 1982 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials/Federal Highway Administration Seminar on Pavements San Diego, California, December 1985 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials Annual Meeting Seattle, Washington, July-October 1985 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials Policy Committee Chicago, Illinois, July-August 1984 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials Annual Meeting New Orleans, Louisiana, January 1984-March 1985 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Pennsylvania State University, June-September 1982 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Pennsylvania State University, June 1982-January 1983 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Pennsylvania State University, February 1978-November 1981 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Matson Fund- Sheraton Hall, September 1977-January 1985 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Joint Center for Urban Mobility- Rice Center, May 1984 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Matson Fund Trustee 1977-79, December 1976-January 1980 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - International Road Federation 1975, March 1975-February 1979 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Associate Administrators for R and D-Peter Benjamin, Ocotber 1980-May 1983 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Meeting With Federal Aviation Administration- Lynn Helms, September-December 1982 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Federal Highway Administration, January 1980-Septpember 1982 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Meeting of Transportation Research Board Representatives with Secretary of Transportation, June 1981-November 1983 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Federal Railroad Administration Presentation, July 1981-May 1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Ray Peck-National Highway Traffic Safety Administration Briefing, March 1980-June 1981 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Ray A. Barnhart- Federal Highway Adminstration Briefing, April 1981 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - American Public Works Association 1984-86, January 1983-September 1986 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Facilities Minutes and Agenda, October 1987-June 1988 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Transportation Research Board Annual Report, December 1982-July 1986 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Inaugural Meeting of Highway Innovative Technology Evaluation Center Executive Committee 1 of 2, May 1993 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Inaugural Meeting of Highway Innovative Technology Evaluation Center Executive Committee 2 of 2, May 1986-May 1993 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Highway Innovative Technology Evaluation Center Executive Committee, October 1992-July 1993 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Highway Innovative Technology Evaluation Center Executive Committee Meeting and Task Force Breakout Sessions, February-November 1993 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Meetings Office Confirmation Forms 1993, August-December 1993 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Engineering News Record Magazine "Building America's Smart Highways 1993" 1 of 2, June-December 1993 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Engineering News Record "Building America's Smart Highways 1993", October-December 1993 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Federal Highway Administration/Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development Seminar, March 1987-October 1993 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Swiss Academy of Engineering Sciences-10th Council of Academies of Engineering and Technological Sciences Convocation, April 1962, December 1992-September 1993 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Meeting of National Center for Asphalt Technology Board of Directors 1993, April-August 1993 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Highway Innovative Technology Evaluation Center Executive Committee Meeting, July-August 1993 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Intermodal, December 1992-July 1993 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Department of Transportation-Office of Secretary-Briefing, June-July 1993 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - International Motor Carrier Symposium, October 1992-June 1993 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - National Policy on Intelligent Transportation Systems, June 1994 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - International Road Federation, March-May 1993 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - The Bay Area Partnership- Oakland Bay Area, California, December 1992-April 1993 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Visiting Committee Draft Minutes, April-December 1993 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Con Expo, November 1990-March 1993 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Center for Transportation Studies- Massachusetts Institute of Technology, October 1992-March 1993 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society of America Retreat 1993, Dallas, Texas, December 1992-February 1993 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - 36th Annual Highway Engineering and Construction Conference- Auburn University, July 1992-February 1993 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society of America Coordinating Council, December 1992-January 1993 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Highway Innovative Technology Evaluation Center Executive Committee Meeting, February-December 1992 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Northeast Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials Research Correlation, May 1986-June 1990 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society of America, July 1994 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Planning Committee, Reston, Virginia, April-July 1994 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Program Plan Public Forums, June 1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - National Policy Conference on Intelligent Transportation Systems and the Environment, May-June 1994 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Meetings and Events, May-June 1994 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Institute of Transportation Engineers Award Presentation, May 1994 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Civil Engineering Visiting Committee Meeting, Austin, Texas, October 1993-May 1994 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Asphalt Institute- Reception and Dinner-ANA Hotel, March-April 1994 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Auburn University Conference Center, Auburn, Alabama, March-April 1994 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Meeting, Atlanta, Georgia, February-April 1994 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Automated Highway System Workshop 1 of 2, October 1993-April 1994 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Automated Highway System Workshop 2 of 2, March 1993-April 1994 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Transportation Roundtable Luncheon, University of Kentucky, February-March 1994 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - National Research Council Seminar- Meetings and Events, February-March 1994 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - National Asphalt Pavement Association-39th Annual Convention National Asphalt Pavement Association, February 1993 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Highway Innovative Technology Evaluation Center Executive Committee Ballot, December 1993-March 1994 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Highway Innovative Technology Evaluation Center Committee Meeting- Madison Hotel, February 1994 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - The American Society of Swedish Engineers, April 1988-June 1994 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Blue Ribbon Advisory Council, January-July 1992 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Indian Highways 1984-86-Article, June 1984-February 1986 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - No Name Committee 1992-94, February 1992-April 1994 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - No Name Committee 1988-91, December 1987-March 1991 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - University of Texas- Committee, August-October 1994 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Wallen Associates Consultants 1988, September 1986-January 1994 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Private Sector Pavement Research 1993-94, January 1981-January 1994 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Coordinating Council Meeting, Minneapolis, June 1991 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Strategic Planning Committee Meeting, April-June 1991 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Itelligent Vehicle Highway Society of America Steering Committee Meeting, Washington, DC, January 1991 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Itelligent Vehicle Highway Society America Coordinating Council Meeting-Holiday Inn Crown Plaza Arlington, Virginia, May-October 1991 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Itelligent Vehicle Highway Society America Coordinating Council Meeting-Holiday Inn Crown Plaza Arlington, Virginia, June-September 1991 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Itelligent Vehicle Highway Society Steering Committee, June 1989-October 1990 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Committees and Committee Members List 1 of 2, June 1991-June 1993 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Committees and Committee Members List 2 of 2, July 1991-April 1993 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society America Board of Directors Retreat, January-February 1993 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Coordinating Council, July 1993-April 1994 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - National Center for Asphalt Technology, April 1993, September 1992-April 1993 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Coordinating Council, Atlanta, Georgia, December 1993-April 1994 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Coordinating Council, January 1993-January 1994 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Planning Meeting- Comments on Plans, October-December 1993 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Board of Directors, June-August 1994 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Board of Directors 1 of 2, August 1992-April 1993 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Board of Directors 2 of 2, November 1992-February 1993 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Coordinating Council 1 of 2, January-April 1993 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Coordinating Council 2 of 2, October 1992-March 1993 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - International Trade Fair for Designing-Management and Maintenance of Traffic and Transport Infrastructures, November 1989-February 1990 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Meeting 1 of 4, January 1993 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Meeting 2 of 4, December 1992-January 1993 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Meeting 3 of 4, September 1992-January 1993 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Meeting 4 of 4, October 1992-February 1993 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society America Coordinating Council 1 of 6, June-July 1994 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society America Coordinating Council 2 of 6, July-August 1994 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society America Coordinating Council 3 of 6, April-August 1994 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society America Coordinating Council 4 of 6, April-July 1994 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society America Coordinating Council 5 of 6, May-July 1994 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society America Coordinating Council 6 of 6, April-October 1994 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Proceedings of a National Workshop on Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society, March 1990 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - 3M- Lake of the Woods, Canada, April-June 1987 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 1.1: Lectures and Speeches, October 1976-March 1994
    At many of the events that Deen attended, he was invited to speak on a variety of topics. Material in this subseries includes transcripts of speeches, notes, programs, correspondence, travel information, maps, organizational charts, articles, pamphlets, schedules, agendas, newsletters, presentation slides, graphs and attendance lists. Subject matter includes Thomas Deen's life, the Transportation Research Board, the 55 mile per hour speed limit, the future of the automobile, economic growth and development, research, transportation, value engineering, citizens band radio in intercity busses, urban policy, trucking, hazardous materials, state and federal financial management, rapid transit, traffic congestion, transportation law, the role of state and region in public surface transportation, transportation centers, infrastructure, highway construction, engineering management, commencement addresses, transportation planning and scholarship.
    - National Asphalt Pavement Association-Hyatt Regency Capitol Hill, March-August 1987 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - 55 mph Speed Limit Congressional Testimony, March 1987 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia, February-March 1985 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Caltrans Speech, Sacramento, California, August-September 1984 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Technology Transfer-Delaware Department of Transportation, November 1981-March 1982 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - The Urban Institute, February-July 1982 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Value Engineering Orlando, Florida, October 1983-May 1984 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Speech to CB Radio Committee, October 1983 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Speech to 3R Conference, September 1983 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - 11th Australian Road Research Board Annual Conference, Melbourne, Australia, August 1982 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Future of the Automobile- Australia Speech, August 1982, October 1976-January 1981 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Evolution of National Urban Policy in the United States- Australia Speech, August 1982, June-August 1982 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Transportation Research Forum, Washington, DC, March-April 1982 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Regular Common Carrier Conference, Marco Island, Florida, November 1981-February 1982 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Texas A and M University, August 1981-February 1982 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - American Road Transportation Builders Association- Road Gang Speech, April-August 1981 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - International Bridge, Tunnel, and Turnpike Association, January-May 1981 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Hazardous Materials and Wastes in Highway 1980s, December 1980-February 1981 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Assembly of Engineering- Presentation, November 1980-January 1981 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - State Federal Financing Meeting-Scottsdale, Arizona, August 1987-September 1988 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Testimony- 55 Mph, March-July 1988 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Senate Testimony, February-March 1988 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Taipei, Taiwan Rapid Transit Study, October 1980-January 1981 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Hawaii Department of Transportation, August-December 1980 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Princeton University Transportation Seminar Lecture, August-November 1980 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Conference- Intercity Bus Transport, September 1980 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Transportation Research Board's Conference on the State and Regional Roles in Public Surface Transportation, August 1980, July-August 1980 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Cincinnati of Cleveland Presentation 1980 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Marine Board, October-December 1988 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Transportation Center- Delaware, October 1989, April-October 1989 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Forum Speech- Federal Aviation Administration, June-August 1989 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Rural Technical Assistance Program-Montana, September 1988-July 1989 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - General Accounting Office Meeting, April-June 1989 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - General Accounting Office, Octobe-December 1988 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Monterey California, May 1979, October 1988 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Institute of Transporation Engineers, January-June 1991 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Transportation Research Forum, May 1991 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - National Asphalt Pavement Association-Dallas, Texas, October 1990-April 1991 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - American Concrete Pavement Association- Scottsdale, Arizona, June-December 1990 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - University of Kentucky Commencement Speech, February 1990-July 1991 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - New Orleans, February-March 1990 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - National Asphalt Pavement Association- Hawaii, March 1989-November 1990 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - TV Lecture, May-November 1992 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - American Public Transportation Association Workshop, June-October 1992 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Institute of Transportation Engineers Conference, April 1991-April 1992 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials 66th Annual Meeting Las Vegas, Nevada, October-December 1980 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials Conference Commissioners- Patsy Thomason Talk Chicago, Illinois, August-October 1981 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials-Baltimore, July-November 1986 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials - Standing Comittee on Planning Meeting Sacramento, California, June 1982-May 1984 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials - Standing Committee on Planning Meeting Sacramento, California, November 1982-March 1984 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials Chief Administrative Officer Symposium Speech, May 1983 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials Annual Meeting Orlando, Florida, October 1981-November 1982 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials Annual Meeting Denver, Colorado, July-October 1983 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania State University, October 1980-June 1982 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Oklahoma Department of Transportation Research Review Day, October 1982-February 1983 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - National Research Council, May-July 1993 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Penn State Lecture Materials 1 of 2, May 1980-September 1981 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Penn State Lecture Materials 2 of 2, December 1979-August 1981 (Box 27, Folder 2)